-=圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hdscg.com/=-
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
翻译: 脸圆圆 灵峰 RK翔 小金鱼骑士 肉肉君
-=圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hdscg.com/=-
协调: 影子  校对: 。沫
想在此处添加您的广告信息？立即联系 www.OpenSubtitles.org
我向你们发誓
I swear to you,
每一个被瘟疫带走的母亲和女儿
every single mother and daughter,
父亲和儿子
father and son taken from us
我都将替他们一一报仇
by the Black Plague will be avenged.
是黑巫后
It is their Witch Queen
将诅咒降临在我们的大陆
who brought this curse upon our lands.
只有她的死亡才能换来我们的救赎
And in her death lies our salvation.
要注意 兄弟们
Be warned, brothers.
在心脏停止跳动前
She will never truly perish
她永远不会真正死亡
until her heart beats its last.
我们要无所畏惧
Let fear be dead to us.
绝不能后退
There is no going back,
因为我们已经无路可退
for there is nothing to go back to.
那是什么 多兰?
What is it, Dolan?
毁灭巫师就在我们身边
The Hexen are amongst us.
这地方到处都是死亡的气息
This place reeks of death.
时刻保持头脑冷静
Keep your wits about you.
跟紧一点
Stay close.
是她!
It's her!
是黑巫后!
It's the Queen!
是魔法
The magic.
后退!
Stay back!
以钢铁和火焰之名!
By iron and fire!
救救我们!
Help us!
- 多兰! - 黑女巫!
- Dolan! - The Queen!
天父啊
Heavenly Father,
保佑我们远离这些魔鬼
protect us from these demons.
啊!
Ah!
保持阵型 兄弟们!
Stay in formation, men!
父亲!
Father!
父亲 我好想你
Father, I missed you.
你不是真的
You're not real.
不可能是真的
You can't be.
你们像老鼠一样繁衍
You breed like rats.
你们住在用岩石堆垒
You put stone on top of stone
建成的肮脏巢穴里
and then live in your own filth.
你们是我们世界的入侵者
You are trespassers on our world.
因此我创造了瘟疫
This is why I created the Plague.
你们每个人都必将毁灭
It's why every one of you must perish.
啊!
Ah!
以钢铁
By iron
和火焰之名
and fire.
你爱的每个人都离你而去
Everyone you love is gone.
我从你眼中就能看出来
I've seen it in your eyes.
你渴望死亡
You wish for death.
今天我们将同归于尽
Today we both die.
我用我的生命诅咒你
I curse you with life.
你将永世不得安宁
To never know peace.
你将孤独地走向世界的尽头
To walk the Earth alone for eternity.
你将永远无法死亡
You will never die.
谢谢
Thank you.
打扰了 小姐?
Excuse me, miss?
先生 有什么事吗?
Sir, how can I help you?
魔法
Magic.
嘿...
Hey...
小心点!
Watch it!
抱歉 都是我的错
Sorry. Totally my fault.
不好意思
Excuse me.
你是巫师猎人
You're the witch hunter.
是的
Yeah.
我什么都没做
I didn't do anything.
给我看看
Let's see it.
看什么?
See what?
快点
Come on.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
机长已经开启...
the Captain has turned on...
幸亏你没把它们弄湿
Be glad you didn't get them wet.
我找这东西有一阵子了
I've been looking for these for a while.
这些都是古代符文
These are ancient runes.
可以操纵天气
They can manipulate weather.
雨 风 寒 炎...
Rain, wind, cold, heat...
而你就这么把它们一起塞在包里?
And you just jammed them together in your bag?
你知道当你把暴风雨符文和湿气符文
You know what you get when you mix a thunderstorm
在40000英尺的高空混合起来后会得到什么吗?
with cool, moist air at 40,000 feet?
这是很简单的科学道理
It's simple science.
简直难以置信
Unbelievable.
你们这些巫师都不知道自己有着怎样的力量
You witches have no idea the power you've got.
哦 天啊
Oh, my God.
你要把我送到巫师委员会去吗?
Are you gonna turn me over to the Witch Council?
不
No.
那你会杀了我吗?
You're gonna kill me?
杀你?
Kill you?
我是在阻止你杀了你自己
I'm tryin' to stop you from killing yourself.
祝你在纽约玩儿得开心
Enjoy New York.
先生 "请系好安全带"的标志亮了
Sir, "Fasten seatbelts" signs are on.
你得回到座位上去
I need you to take a seat.
我叫卡尔德
My name is Kaulder.
请您回到座位上 卡尔德
I need you to get back to your seat, Kaulder.
我很想听听你小时候在塞夫鲁的经历
I'd love to hear about growing up in Sefrou.
你怎么知道的?
How'd you know?
我已经很多年说话没有口音了
Haven't had an accent in years.
我这辈子见过很多的人
I've met a lot of people in my life.
一定会让你大吃一惊的
You'd be amazed what you pick up.
巫师们秘密地生活在人群之中
Witches live among us in secret.
他们的魔力继承自原始种族
Their magic passed down from an ancient race,
已逐渐淡化 遗忘 但是仍然危险而强大
diluted, half-forgotten, but dangerously powerful.
经过几个世纪的冲突 巫师与人类之间达成了休战协议
After centuries of conflict, a truce was forged.
人类允许巫师
Witches would be allowed to live
在世间生存 自治
and govern themselves if they followed
前提是他们严格遵守规定 永远不对人类使用魔法
one strict rule, that magic never be used against humans.
但休战协议是个脆弱的东西
But a truce is a fragile thing.
有些女巫渴望着
There are some who long for
重拾曾经的生活
the return of the old ways,
被黑巫后统治的黑暗时代
the dark days of the Witch Queen.
卡尔德需要解决的就是这些女巫
It is those whom Kaulder deals with.
800年以来 他效命于十字斧教
For 800 years, he has served The Axe and Cross.
与我们共同看守女巫 保护和平
Together we have kept watch and kept the peace.
呃 很抱歉 多兰神父 他在开会
Uh, I'm sorry, Father Dolan. He's in a meeting.
哦
Oh.
会议已经结束了
The meeting has concluded.
我以一种截然不同的方式
I serve The Axe and Cross
效命于十字斧教
in a very different manner.
我是第36代多兰 我书写卡尔德的历史
I am the 36th Dolan, and I write Kaulder's history.
我是他的管理者 他的倾听者
I am his handler, his confessor,
我也乐于认为 自己是他的朋友
and, I like to think, his friend.
你完全没有时间观念
You have no sense of time.
我当然有 只不过跟你的不一样
Course I do. It's just different than yours.
我猜你的任务很成功?
I assume your mission was a success?
你平安无事地找到了天气符文?
You recovered the weather runes without incident?
我给你的iPad哪去了?
What happened to the iPad I gave you?
借花献佛了
I re-gifted it.
我们不像你那么适应现代科技
We're not all as adaptable as you.
你知道纸张已经过时了吧
You know paper's the past.
它还是非常有用的记录工具
It's also a useful object on which to record it.
你是在回忆路德维希事件吗?
Are you reminiscing about the Ludwig affair?
我现在伤感着呢
I'm in a sentimental mood.
啊
Ah.
因为我的退休?
About my retirement?
所以你回来了
That's why you've come back.
我们一直配合得很好
We have had a good run.
我们解决了许多邪恶的女巫集会
We took out some nasty covens.
你真的准备不干了吗?
You're really ready to call it quits?
区区50年而已
It's only been 50 years.
我好不容易习惯了你
I'm finally getting used to you.
哦 这就是全部原因?
Oh. Is that all it took?
我会想你的 孩子
I'll miss you, kid.
这是支华特曼402钢笔
This is a Waterman 402.
我在上面刻了你的名字缩写
I had your initials engraved on it.
这笔非常稀少
It's very rare.
刻过字后价值恐怕大大缩水了
Probably lowered the value quite a bit.
对我来说可不是
Not to me.
你再好好考虑一下 笔就是你的
You reconsider, you can still keep the pen.
我想你会喜欢我的接班人的
I think you'll like my successor.
我准备用现代点的方法离开你
I'm leaving you in more modern hands.
你曾经说过的誓约呢?
What about the vow you took?
我的誓约是在你身边直至死亡
I vowed to face death at your side.
而不是工作到挂掉
Not to work until I keel over.
第35代多兰在你之前来过这里
Thirty-five Dolans have come before you.
这杯敬唯一能让我
Here's to the only one
听取建议的人
whose advice I ever listened to.
虽然你从来不肯照办
Only to ignore it.
但我永远都会听的
But I always listen.
如果你也退休了呢?
What if you were retiring, too?
我是说 如果你的下个任务
I mean, what would you do
就是最后一个任务你会怎么办?
if your next mission was your last?
不可能的
But it won't be.
配合我一下
Humor me.
我一直毫无怨言
I have no complaints.
每天我醒来
Every day I wake up,
这个世界都会更轻松地睡去
the world sleeps a little easier.
卡尔德 你经历过
Kaulder, you have tasted more of life
我无法想象的长久人生
than I can ever imagine,
但是你已经很久没有真正的活过了
but it's been a long time since you really lived.
你享受不到我们短暂的生命中
You're missing out on the best part
最美好的那一部分
of our brief stay in this world.
和人分享的那一部分
The part where you share it.
找个信任的人吧
Find someone to trust.
我信任你
I trust you.
可能要再找个清秀一点儿的
Perhaps someone a little more comely.
我知道 我并不像你一样
I know, I haven't lived
拥有悠久而丰富的人生
as long and rich a life as you,
但我同样清楚 人生的意义远不止
but I do know that there is more to it
欣赏一群空姐
than a parade of stewardesses
和着月光鸣奏曲进行游行
marching to the dulcet tones of Moonlight Sonata.
你到底是怎么知道
Now what in the world do you know
空姐的事儿的?
about stewardesses anyway?
我又不是生来就是神父
I wasn't born a priest.
我们来干点活吧
Let's do some work.
我知道你觉得这很无聊
I know you think it's dull,
不过我们还是得从头开始
but let's start at the beginning.
虽然是不言而喻的事
It goes without saying,
但您效力的方式真是与众不同
but you've served with great distinction.
冒昧一问 我明天见卡尔德的时候
If I may, when I meet Kaulder tomorrow,
需要冷静一点 是吗?
I should play it cool, right?
仪式完毕再去喝咖啡之类的
No coffee until after the ritual.
别担心什么风度了
Don't worry about your style.
反正无论如何他都会嘲讽你的
He'll take the piss out of you anyway.
但你会没事的
But you'll be fine.
只是 呃 我担心的是卡尔德
It's, uh, Kaulder that I worry about.
你担心卡尔德?
You worry about Kaulder?
你知道十字斧教的前辈们
Do you know how the elders
是如何看待他的吗?
of The Axe and Cross refer to him?
他们称他为 "秘密武器"
They call him "The Weapon."
当我提交报告时
When I put in my reports,
他们所关心的只有数字
all they want to know is numbers.
我移交了多少女巫
How many witches I've turned over for detention.
又有多少女巫因为违反法律被处死
How many slain for breaking the law.
这能怪他们吗? 他所做的事情是如此的重要
Can you blame them? What he does is so important.
是的 的确很重要 但他不仅仅是个武器
Yes, that's true, but he isn't just a weapon.
而我们这些知道真相的人
And those of us who know the truth,
必将肩负重任
we bear responsibility.
无论发生什么 发誓你会看好他
Whatever happens, promise me you'll watch out for him.
当然 这是我的工作
Of course. That's my job.
出租车!
Taxi!
你好?
Hello?
卡尔德先生吗?
Kaulder?
第36代多兰昨晚走的很安详
Dolan the 36th passed away peacefully last night.
仪式将在明天举行
The ceremony will be tomorrow.
对此我感到很遗憾
I'm sorry for your loss.
在你之前已有三十六任"多兰"了
Thirty-six have taken the name "Dolan" before you.
你是否有资格成为合格的第三十七任?
Are you worthy of becoming the 37th?
我会用行动证明的
I testify that I am.
你会发誓全力
Do you promise to serve
协助卡尔德吗?
our brother Kaulder in all things?
你愿意成为他的知己吗?
To know him only as he knows himself?
我发誓
I promise.
你就是那个新人
So you're the new guy.
其实我们之前见过
We've actually met before.
很早以前
A long time ago.
你瞧见那些基石了吗?
You see that cornerstone?
我看着它们在玉米地上
I watched them lay it in
一点点地砌筑起来
when this was nothing more than a cornfield.
那才叫很早以前
That was a long time ago.
作为第三十七任多兰 我将自己的生命与忠诚交于你
I pledge my life and loyalty to you as the 37th Dolan.
我发誓助你完成组织赋予你的使命...
I swear to help you carry out your duty to the Order...
他们建造这座城市时
When they were building this city,
建筑工人在十八米深的地方
construction crews discovered
发现了一座巨大的墓地
a mass gravesite, 60 feet below ground,
那个被遗忘的角落堆满了几千具奴隶尸体
filled with thousands of forgotten slaves.
知道他们怎么处理的吗?
Know what they did?
不知道
No.
日夜赶工 填平墓地
Worked by night, filled the hole,
继续建造
and kept building.
邪恶无所不在
There are shades of evil everywhere.
我为你准备了
So, I'm sorting you out with
新的信用卡 护照 还有身份证
fresh credit cards, new passport, and a new identity.
我已经习惯用旧的了
Just gettin' used to the old one.
但它们都过期了
Well, it's out of date.
如今的电视台 手机和定位系统
There are global databases now, CCTV's,
都使用全球联网数据库了 世界正在改变
smartphones and geotracking. The world is changing.
只是表面上的改变而已
Only on the surface.
这么说也没错 不过还是要低调点
Right. But it's important to keep a low profile.
幸亏这辆车不是红色的
I guess we should be thankful it's not red.
我能问问要去哪里吗?
May I ask where we're going?
我虽然见过别人衰老 退休 去世
I've seen people get old, retire, and die.
但是罕有都在同一天的
Rarely on the same day.
他死在桌子前
He was found at his desk.
我们要找什么?
What are we looking for?
如何知道这附近是否使用过魔法?
How do you know when there's magic in the vicinity?
巫师的魔法来自四种元素
A witch's magic comes from four elements,
火 水 土 气
fire, water, earth and air.
只要用恰当的炼金术触发
Applying the correct alchemical triggers
就能让这些元素显现
will reveal its presence.
这里没有魔法
No magic here.
我只想确认一下
Just wanted to be sure.
如果窗户始终是关着的话
If the window hasn't been opened,
这些东西是怎么进来的?
how did that get in here?
只有一个 也许没事
One means nothing.
只有两个 那也可能是巧合
Two, a coincidence.
如果有三个 就是大大的麻烦了
Three, trouble.
趴下!
Get down!
怎么回事?
What?
他是被巫师杀害的
He was killed by witches.
十字斧教的历代多兰
Never in the history of The Axe and Cross
没有一任是被谋杀的
has a Dolan ever been murdered.
你想退出了?
You wanna quit?
不想
No.
我要加薪
I want a raise.
这是在宣战
This is a declaration of war.
谁会这么做?
Who could have done this?
他们使用了隐匿咒
A concealment spell was placed
好让一切看起来正常
to make everything look normal.
他们在找一样东西
They were searching for something,
但不想被我们发现
didn't want us to know.
元素魔法是中性的
Elemental magic is neutral.
追根究底 它并没有好坏之分
At its root it's neither good nor evil.
但这个不同
But this is different.
这是黑魔法
This is dark magic.
非常邪恶
Beyond evil.
他们把他绑在椅子上
They tied him to the chair.
"死亡"
"Death."
那是咒语的一部分吗?
Is that part of the spell?
昨晚 在他死之前你也在这里 对吗?
You were here last night before he died, right?
对
Yes.
让我看看你的手
Let me see your hands.
马上
Now.
在我五岁时
I was five years old
巫师放火烧了我的家
when witches set our house on fire.
我父母死了
My parents died.
是你走过火焰
But you walked through the flames,
把我裹在毯子里
wrapped me in a blanket,
跳出了二楼窗户
and jumped out the second story window.
坠落时 你用身体护住了我
Your body broke the fall.
我说了之前我们见过
I told you we'd met before.
如果你忘了 我再告诉你一些细节...
If you don't remember, I can refer you to the entry...
我没忘
No. I remember.
你追捕那些巫师 将他们绳之以法
You hunted down the witches and brought them to justice.
我一直在等待一个帮助你的机会
I've waited my entire life for the opportunity to help you.
这就是你的机会
Well, now's your chance.
帮我找出真凶
You can help me hunt the witches that did this.
我不该带把枪或者铁槌什么的?
Shouldn't I have a gun or an iron mallet or something?
深呼吸 放松点
Take a deep breath. Center yourself.
当然
Right. Of course.
因为头脑清醒才能抵抗魔法
Because resisting enchantment requires a clear mind.
听我说 麦克斯是一个十四级的男巫
Now, Max is a 14th level warlock,
你抵抗不了的 还不如放轻松
there's nothing you can do. May as well relax.
神父 要尝尝样品吗?
Free sample, Father?
谢谢
Oh. Thank you.
如果是我 就不会轻易下嘴
I'd think twice about that.
我没想到能赚一万美金
I don't know that I can do $10,000.
你很清楚这些虫子
You know the level of enchantment
能对他们造成多大的影响
they are getting from that.
生意不错吧?
Business is good, right?
是的
Yeah.
见鬼
Oh, crap.
关门了 麦克斯
Shop's closed, Max.
卡尔德 好久不见了
Kaulder. It has been too long.
贩卖致幻虫也不犯法吧
It is not illegal to sell mind-altering bugs.
如果用在人身上 就算犯法了
When they're used on humans, it is.
他们把虫子掺进了杯形蛋糕里
They're mixing them in the cupcakes.
我看不到
I hadn't noticed.
那这个呢?
Notice this?
格里芬天仙子 极其罕见并且禁止使用
Griffin's Henbane. Very rare and forbidden.
这是在巫术中使用的 黑魔法
This is used in necromancy. Dark magic.
你知道我不卖这种邪恶的东西
You know I do not deal in these kinds of bad things.
麦克斯 你总不至于犯这种蠢吧
Max, you're too smart to go down that road.
我听过的谎言多到令人难以想象
One can only imagine how many times I've been lied to.
比史上任何人听过的都多
More than anyone in history, actually.
拜托 卡尔德
Come on, Kaulder.
你必须明白 任何人只要敢用这种草
You must understand, anyone who would use this herb
就不会怕你 而这一点吓到我了!
is not afraid of you. And that scares me!
你怕这个 却不怕我?
More than I scare you?
麦克斯
Max.
那个来找我的人皮肤上有种气味
The man who came to see me has an odor on his skin.
闻起来像大蒜 却又不是
A whiff of garlic that was not garlic.
砒霜 还有吗?
Arsenic. Anything else?
腐烂的山楂味
And moldering crabapples.
多谢 麦克斯
Thank you, Max.
小心点
Be careful.
没那个习惯
Not in the habit.
不是你 是他
Not you. Him.
所以 你听懂了吗?
So, all that made sense to you?
你不懂吗?
It didn't to you?
不懂
No.
在内战时期 砒霜被用在尸体防腐上
Arsenic was used for embalming back in the Civil War.
谋杀多兰的那个人
Whoever killed Dolan
很可能住在一个曾经是殡仪馆的地方
is likely living in what was once a funeral parlor.
我们只要找周围有山楂树的就行了
We just have to find one with a crabapple tree.
这是干嘛?
What's that for?
自己打车走
A cab.
接下来的事情你应付不了
You're not qualified for what happens next.
哦
Oh.
好的 我会拿小票的
Right. I'll get a receipt.
哇哦
Whoa.
你妈妈没教你不要吃树上的糖果吗?
Didn't your mother ever teach you not to eat candy from trees?
快回家 孩子
Go home, kid.
走开
Go away.
没事的
It's okay.
- 离我远点 - 嘘
- Get away from me. - Shh.
没事的
It's okay.
别再靠近了
Get away from me now.
- 我不会伤害你的 - 走开!
- I'm not gonna hurt you. - Go away!
没事的
It's okay.
该死
Oh, shit.
你为什么要杀多兰?
You killed Dolan. Why?
谁他妈的是多兰? 哈?
Who the bloody hell's Dolan? Huh?
我这辈子都没见过!
I never met the man in my life!
喜欢我的新钢笔吗? 哈?
Do you like my new pen? Huh?
我想象过自己第一次在
When I imagined my first prosecution
委员会前起诉的场景
in front of the Council,
可我从未想过
I never thought it would be
死者会是自己人
for a crime against one of our own.
埃里克·拉马斯内尔
Ellic Lemasniel.
你好啊 神父 呜呼!
Hello, Father. Whoo!
你看起来是个好人
You look like a good man,
故作高雅的小人 我从没去过...
tasty little thing, you. I never went...
请别因此看轻我
Please don't think less of me.
过后我会忏悔的
I'll confess it later.
巫师委员会在此恭候
The Witch Council receives you,
十字斧教的第三十七任多兰
37th Dolan of The Axe and Cross.
愿和平永存
The peace endures.
疑犯埃里克·拉马斯内尔
I present the accused,
被指控谋杀第三十六任多兰
Ellic Lemasniel, for judgment,
在此接受审判
for the murder of Dolan the 36th.
这是在被告住所找到的证据
I present the evidence found in the accused's dwelling.
找到的? 太轻描淡写了吧
Found? Oh, come on.
看什么? 你们看起来像是八十年代的垃圾乐队
What? You look like a terrible band from the '80s.
看看你们的发型!
Look at your hair!
他将接受审判
He will be judged.
巴拉 巴拉 巴拉
Blah, blah, blah.
你知道吗 我曾祖父的祖父
You know my great-grandfather's
曾侍候过黑巫后
grandfather served The Queen, huh?
黑巫后
The Queen.
你们不过是官僚机构的胆小鬼
You're a bureaucracy o' cowards
我不承认这个委员会的权威
and I don't recognize the authority here in this council.
也不用遵守你们的法律
Nor do I abide by your law.
法律是用来控制和规范魔法的使用
The laws serve to control and contain magic.
只有依靠委员会的正常运行
It is only by the operations of this council
才能避免战争的发生
that another war does not begin.
我不撒谎! 我为自己的行为感到骄傲!
I won't lie! I'm proud of what I done!
我杀了你们的神父!
I murdered your priest!
我把他像猪一样绑住 让他的血一点点流干!
I drip-dried him like he was a stuck pig!
我们的神父 也是我的朋友
Our priest, and my friend.
卡尔德
Kaulder.
见鬼 又是这个人
Oh, shit. This guy again.
在审判他之前不先审问一下吗?
So we're to judge him without interrogation?
有人问过他是否有同谋吗?
Has anyone asked him who he was workin' with?
星币三这张牌没有出现
There's no Three of Pentacles card.
也就意味着他是独立行动的
That means he worked alone.
塔罗牌错了
The cards are wrong.
他用了一个变形咒
He cast a shape-shifting spell.
我已经八百年没见过这种咒语了
I haven't seen that crafted in 800 years.
黑巫后死后就再没见过
Not since the time of the Witch Queen.
哈! 黑巫后早就死了
Ha! The Witch Queen is long dead.
她的魔法不可能现世了
That her magic could return is impossible.
- 真的不可能吗? - 是的
- Is it impossible? - It is.
- 你有能力... - 够了!
- You have the authority... - Enough!
把这个城市调查个底朝天
to turn this city inside out.
鉴于非法使用魔法...
For the crimes of illegal crafting...
找出他替谁卖命
Find who he's working with.
以及杀害人类的罪行...
and human sacrifice...
- 我为自己的行为感到骄傲 - 我们判决...
- And I'm proud o' what I done. - we sentence...
埃里克·拉马斯内尔...
Ellic Lemasniel...
我没什么好遗憾的了
I'm proud o' what I done.
- 囚禁于... - 我问心无愧!
- to incarceration... - I took a stand!
本密室深处岩床中
in the bedrock beneath this chamber.
苏醒吧 守卫
Arise, Sentinel,
将这个犯人送进监牢
and carry the condemned to prison.
你将被永囚于黑暗
You'll never see daylight again.
不 不! 你也许能困住我
No, no! You may hold me now,
但你困不住我们所有人!
but you'll never have us all!
这是什么?
What is that?
嘿 孩子
Hey, kid.
你要做什么?
What are you doing?
你好 神父
Hello, Father.
挺住啊 老伙计
Still with us, old friend.
他还活着?
He's alive?
快不行了
Barely.
他被诅咒了
He's been cursed.
怎么会?
How?
蝇马利
Musca Mali.
瘟疫蝇
Plague fly.
13世纪的黑魔法
13th-century black magic.
源自黑巫后之树 对吧?
They were created in the tree of the Queen, correct?
是的
That's right.
为什么他们不直接杀了他?
Why didn't they just murder him?
他们想先审问他
They wanted to interrogate him.
一旦瘟疫蝇钻进你身体里
When a Plague fly burrows inside of you,
它就霸占了你的意识
it breaks your will.
不管凶手想知道什么
Whatever the killers wanted to know,
多兰都会说出来
he would have told them.
但问题是 他们到底想知道什么?
But the question remains, what did they want to know?
他没醒过来
He isn't getting up.
除非我们能破除诅咒
Not unless we could break the curse.
而唯一的办法
And the only way to do that
就是杀掉下咒的巫师
is to kill the witch who cast it.
那个埃里克效命的人
The one Ellic works for.
多兰最多只能撑两天
Dolan's got two days, tops.
为了我 坚持住
Hang in there, for me.
死亡
Death.
那是多兰留的消息 不是凶手留的
It's a message from Dolan, not the killer.
"回忆你的死亡"
"Remember your death."
什么意思?
What does it mean?
唯一能让我回想起自己的死亡的...
There's only one way to remember my death...
只有魔法
Magic.
嗨 克洛伊
Hey, Chloe.
这边还有一杯
I have one more drink here.
- 你们玩得开心吗? - 不错
- Are you guys okay? - Yeah, we're good.
帅哥们 晚上过得好吗?
Are we having a good night, gentlemen?
宝贝 和我一起喝杯爱酒吧
Do a love shot with me, baby.
哦 算了 我今晚不求爱
Oh, no. I'm not looking for love tonight.
- 你们还好吗? - 很好
- You guys okay? - Yep.
哦 不 有没有搞错! 别啊 你不能走
Oh, no, come on! No, not you, too.
我听说 他是个特别反复无常的人
I heard that you can't tell before it happens. Okay?
开头还是一派冷静的样子 接着...
He's just standing there all chilly calm, and then...
刷! 砍下了你的头
Wham! He cuts your head off
系在他裤腰带上
and puts it in a sack on his belt.
拜托! 这只是保姆讲给孩子们听
C'mon! That's just a story nannies tell children
吓唬他们的
so they behave.
克洛伊 快走吧
Chloe, you need to leave.
米兰达 米兰达!
Miranda. Miranda!
我们守规矩的 这里没有人类
We're up to code. There are no humans here.
地方不错啊
Beautiful place.
谢谢
Thank you.
你们怎么收费?
How much do you charge?
那要看你买什么了
Well, that depends on what you're buying.
一段记忆
A memory.
五百美金
Five hundred dollars.
成交
Deal.
我刚刚说了"百"? 其实...
Did I just say "Hundred"? I...
说错了 我其实是想说"五千美金"
No, you know what? I actually meant "Five thousand."
五千 你确定了吗?
Five thousand, is that what you meant?
确定 是"五千美金"
I did. I meant "Five thousand."
成交
Sold.
五万美金
Fifty thousand.
可以开始了吗?
Shall we start?
不 什么来着? 算了
No. You know what? No.
我改主意了 我要关...
I changed my mind. We're cl...
恐惧药水
Fear potion.
你会害怕什么?
Now, what in the world would you be afraid of?
演讲
Public speaking.
你知道我怕什么吗?
You know what I'm afraid of?
说吧
Enlighten me.
还真没怕的 这种生活可无聊了
Nothing. It's boring, really.
听着 我知道你做事讲规矩
See now, I know that you have a code.
我也知道 我没做错什么
And I also know that I haven't done anything wrong,
所以除非你准备一枪打爆我 不然的话 恕不远送
so unless you're gonna put a gun to my head, get out.
你没说错 我是讲规矩的
You know, you're right. I do have a code.
但我也不会就这么走了
But I'm also not leaving.
话说 你要记忆药水做什么?
What do you want a memory potion for, anyway?
你是在猎巫吗?
Are you hunting a witch?
为了帮助一个老朋友
To help an old friend.
事先提醒
But a word of warning to you.
如果在记忆中受伤
If you get injured in your memory,
你的肉体也会遭受相同伤害
you get injured out here.
也就是说 如果记忆中的你死了
Which means to say that if you die in there,
你就真的会死...
you will also die...
我反正是不死身
I can't die anywhere.
就是个保险上的免责协议罢了
I have to make a disclaimer for my insurance.
我先干了
Bottoms up.
说"巫师猎人"
Say "Witch hunter."
巫师猎人
Witch hunter.
老实点
Be nice.
"回忆你的死亡"
"Remember your death."
你到底想要我看什么?
What did you want me to see?
卡尔德!
Kaulder!
卡尔德
Kaulder.
卡尔德 醒醒
Kaulder, wake up.
你好啊 巫师猎人
Well, hello, witch hunter.
我也曾经被人从记忆咒语中强拉出来过
I was yanked out of a memory spell once.
脑子迷糊了好几个小时
My mind was scrambled eggs for hours.
要知道 人类不该去寻找过去
You know, people shouldn't root around in their past.
有些事情 还是忘记比较好
Some things are best left forgotten.
啊...
Ah...
你诅咒了我朋友
You cursed my friend.
你的朋友
Your friend,
他比大多数人多坚持了5分钟
he lasted about five minutes longer than most.
当你死不掉的时候 酒吧斗殴
Doesn't take much balls to get in a bar fight
都不用先壮胆了吧
when you can't get hurt.
可惜你的思维没有...
Too bad your mind isn't as tough
你身体这么强壮
as the rest of you.
不会有酒吧了
No more bar.
也不会有记忆药水了
No more memory potions for you.
呼吸啊
Breathe.
800年了 你的气数也该用尽了
After 800 years, you've run out of time.
死期将至 巫师猎人!
Death is coming, witch hunter!
你和别人说的恶魔没两样
You are the monster they say you are.
都怪你! 这是我全部家当了!
Damn you! This place was all I had!
克洛伊!
Chloe!
抓住我的手!
Grab my hand!
地方不错啊
Nice view.
坚持住 孩子
Just hold on, kid.
我发誓 我会找出凶手 破除诅咒
I promise I'll find who did this and break the curse.
卡尔德! 看这个!
Kaulder! Come see this!
我接入联邦调查局数据库了
I've got the FBI database online.
等等 倒回去
Stop, go back one.
继续
Continuing.
不是 不是他
No, not him.
停下
Stop.
就是他
That's him.
为什么他不想我回忆起自己的死?
But why doesn't he want me to remember my death?
姓名 巴尔塔萨·凯托拉
Born Baltasar Ketola.
又名贝利亚 芬兰国籍
Goes by Belial. Finnish national.
他就是埃里克卖命的主子
He's the one Ellic was working for.
就是他诅咒了多兰?
The one who cursed Dolan?
为了毁灭这世界
Every generation has to be given
巫师还真是一代代不死不休啊
their chance to destroy the world.
但我们大部分人和他不同
Yet most of us aren't like him, you know.
我们和你们差不多
We're the same as you.
你的外貌也许和我们相似 内里却不同
You may look like us, but you're not.
你血液中流淌着魔法
You've got magic in your blood.
足以酿成大祸的魔法
Magic that can do very bad things.
之前在你酒吧 我们被打断了
We were interrupted back in your bar.
- 哦 是哦 - 我必须再试一次
- Oh, yes. - I have to try again.
是哦 我的酒吧!
Yes, my bar!
我在乎的所有东西都付诸一炬了
Where everything I cared about burnt to the ground.
但我不是在怪你毁了我的生活
But I'm not blaming you for destroying
或是其他什么东西
my life or anything.
我恨的是自己只能冷眼旁观
I'm just making an observation.
看着你怎么毁掉我的一切
An observation on how you destroyed my life.
我走了
I'm leaving.
听着 我也不想事情变成这样
Look, I don't like it any more than you do,
但如果你帮助我 我会保证你的人身安全
but if you help me, I promise to keep you safe.
我需要雪墩山柳菊
I'll need more Snowdonia hawkweed
配新的记忆药水
to mix another memory potion.
我手下一个姑娘米兰达
Miranda, the girl who works for me,
有一大批存货
has a pretty good stash.
我短信她
Um, I'll text her.
谢谢
Thank you.
贝利亚的夹克上有红色的土
Belial had red soil on his jacket.
红土?
Red soil?
分析一下 看看有什么结果
Analyze this and see what we get.
好的
Of course.
是米兰达
It's Miranda.
她喜欢猫
She's a cat person.
嗨! 嗨
Hey! Hey, there.
没有 我还活着
No, I'm not dead yet.
好了 等她来了
Right, so when she gets here,
不要乱动啊 好吗?
don't make any sudden moves, okay?
别和她眼神接触
Don't make eye contact.
也不要说话
Or talk.
哇哦
Whoa.
抱歉
Sorry.
就是这个了
This is it here.
不行 这个还没发芽呢
No, it hasn't sprouted yet.
你到底加了多少
How many witch hunter
巫师猎人交流群?
discussion groups are you a part of?
"永生的屠杀狂魔法西斯..."
"Genocidal immortal fascist..."
你们巫师是这么形容我的吗?
So that's what you witches think of me, huh?
那人类又是怎么形容我们的呢?
What is it that people know about us, anyway?
绿皮肤
That we have green skin
戴着尖顶帽
and like to wear pointy hats,
脾气暴躁
and that we're mean
被烧死在塞勒姆的火刑柱上?
and got burned at the stake in Salem?
塞勒姆小镇的事是错的
Salem was wrong,
那些女人是无辜的
And those women innocent.
如果那些女人真的是巫师呢?
But what if those women really were witches?
她们就活该被烧死吗?
Would it then have been okay?
我记得自己想过 如果是我被判刑的话
See, I remember thinking if it was me found guilty,
没人会在乎
no one would care.
我在乎
I would.
山柳菊没了 它不见了
The hawkweed's gone. It's gone.
有人把它拿走了 它不在这了
I mean, someone's taken it. It's not here.
卡尔德?
Kaulder?
怎么了?
What?
- 怎么了? - 别看
- What? - No.
是米兰达
Miranda.
米兰达!
Miranda!
你来晚了 巫师猎人
You're too late, witch hunter.
她死的真惨 既恐惧
She died badly, screaming.
又孤单
Alone.
就和你将来的下场一样
Just like you will.
你会抓到凶手的 对吗?
You're gonna get who did this, right?
我会解决贝利亚的
I'll handle Belial.
很好
Good.
我不知道还有哪里能弄到所需的材料
I don't know where else to get the stuff that we need.
有一个地方
There is one place.
不过那里充斥着旧货币 古魔法 非常危险
But it's old money, old magic, and dangerous.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
卡尔德?
Kaulder?
索尼娅
Sonya.
丹妮卡可是个大忙人
Danique's been so busy,
我很讶异她竟会同意见你
I'm surprised that she agreed to see you.
我想她不会喜欢
I don't think she would have liked
另一个选择的后果
the alternative.
卡尔德先生 很高兴你今晚能来
Mr. Kaulder, you've made my night.
请坐
Please have a seat.
你是从哪里捡来这个小朋友的 二手商店?
Where'd you rescue your little friend from, a thrift shop?
小朋友...
Little friend....
告诉我 什么事那么急?
So tell me, what is this emergency?
你有什么必须要想起来的?
What is it you just must remember?
他丢了他的车钥匙
He lost his car keys.
我要给你多少钱?
How much do I owe you?
一分钱也不用 只要你陪我喝一杯就好
Oh, nothing. You have a drink with me. That's my price.
你知道我为何而来
You know what I'm here for.
芸芸众生都试图伪装自己
So many of us pretend to be something that we're not.
可是你 却真实的活着
But you, you've lived.
你穿越了历史的长河
A man who's walked through history.
你见过拿破仑 斯大林
To have known Napoleon, Stalin,
希特勒...
Hitler...
别怀旧了 这个时代已经够邪恶了
No need to be nostalgic. We have enough evil now.
他们和你没有太大的不同
They're not so different than you.
他们用自己的力量来改变世界
They used their power to change the world.
你不能改变过去所做之事
You can't change what you've done.
卡尔德! 这株植物有点不对劲
Kaulder! There's something wrong with this plant.
你来了
You're here.
卡尔德...
Kaulder...
卡尔德! 卡尔德!
Kaulder! Kaulder!
- 欢迎来到天堂 - 卡尔德!
- Enjoy paradise. - Kaulder!
卡尔德 那些烟 别...
Kaulder, it's smoke. Don't...
看 父亲 看!
Look, Daddy. Look!
它们要飞到南方过冬了
They're flying south for the winter.
卡尔德 听我说
Kaulder, listen to me.
你中了陷阱 我需要你醒来
You are in a trap and I need you to wake up.
你在这里是找不到答案的
You're not gonna find any answers here.
呆的时间越长 你就越难离开
The longer you wait, the harder it is to get out.
卡尔德 卡尔德
Kaulder. Kaulder.
我需要你醒来 这一切都不是真实的
I need you to wake up. None of this is real.
卡尔德 你中计了!
Kaulder, you are in a trap!
快回来
Come back.
卡尔德 如果你不马上醒来
Kaulder, if you don't wake up right now,
我们都会死的!
we are both going to die!
快醒醒!
Wake up!
克洛伊...
Chloe...
这不是真的
This isn't real.
卡尔德! 快醒醒!
Kaulder! Wake up!
把车开到巷子里
Pull the car into the alley
然后把他扔进后备箱
and throw him in the trunk.
我们将因为打败巫师猎人
We're going down in history
而闻名于世了
as the ones who beat the witch hunter.
拜托
Come on.
出去
Get out.
葬土
Burial dirt.
是黑暗魔法最强大的原料
Nothing more powerful for dark magic.
贝利亚要用它来做什么?
What does Belial want with it?
谁?
Who?
"回忆我的死亡"
"Remember my death."
他到底不想让我知道什么?
What is it that he doesn't want me to see?
住手! 拜托了
Stop! Please.
贝利亚什么也没告诉我
Belial didn't tell me anything.
我只负责帮他弄到土
I helped him get the dirt.
我自己私藏了一丁点
I just took a little bit for myself.
可他有一大堆
He has tons of it.
拜托了?
Please?
谢谢你的酒
Thanks for the drink.
你这个巫师族的叛徒!
You are a traitor to your kind!
你知道我为什么喜欢旧货商店吗?
You know what I like about thrift shops?
因为那里的一切都是老的
Everything in them is old.
贱人
Bitch.
现在你知道了
So now you know.
你是一个梦行者
You're a dream-walker.
人人都知道梦行是一种黑暗的天赋
Everyone knows that dream-walking is a black gift.
我一辈子都在试图隐藏它
I've spent my entire life trying to hide from it.
你知道我会发现你的秘密 可你并不在乎
You knew I would discover your secret, and you didn't care.
你还是义无反顾地将我拉出陷阱
You still pulled me out of that trap.
那真是非常勇敢的举动
It was a very brave thing to do.
我有东西要给你看 来吧
Let me show you something. Come on.
晚安 麦克斯!
Good night, Max!
你是我族的耻辱
You are a disgrace to our kind.
贝利亚 我别无选择
Belial, I had no choice.
卡尔德威胁说要把我活活打死
Kaulder threatened to beat me to death with his bare hands.
我们会处置你的 叛徒
We have plans for you, traitor.
你得理解我 贝利亚
You must understand, Belial.
好好享受那些影子吧
Enjoy the shadows.
这是巫师的历史 你们的历史
This is the history of witches. Your history.
那是你
That's you.
对
Yeah.
至少眼睛很形象
Least they got your eyes right.
这些都是梦行者
These are the dream-walkers.
黑巫后身边最致命的刺客
The Witch Queen's deadliest assassins.
他们会用某种方式进入你的脑中
Somehow they used to jump into your mind
窥探你最珍贵的记忆
and pry out your most precious memories.
并把它们转化成你最可怕的噩梦
And then they'd twist 'em into your worst nightmares.
你是在给我上历史课
What, you're giving a history lesson here
还是只为了吓我?
or you're just trying to scare me?
关于梦行者 有一件事无人知晓
There's something no one knows about dream-walkers.
他们不需要什么记忆药水
They don't need memory potions.
那种力量是他们与生俱来的
That power lies within them.
我的脑海深处有一样
I have something buried deep in my mind
必须回想起来的事
that I must remember.
你是唯一一个能帮助我找回记忆的人
And you're the only one that can help me.
不 我不行
No, I can't.
克洛伊...
Chloe...
我不行
No, I can't.
我有一个小弟弟
You know, I have a younger brother,
而且...
and, uh,
他总有办法把我惹恼
he had this knack for just pissing me off.
有一天他做得太过了
And one day he pushed it too far,
于是不知怎的 我进入了他的脑中
and I somehow entered his mind.
虽然不是故意的 可是我伤害了他
I hurt him. I didn't mean to,
狠狠地伤害了他
but I hurt him badly.
所以我逃走了
So I ran away.
你的妻女 她们的名字是什么?
What were their names, your wife and daughter?
我妻子叫海伦娜
Helena.
女儿叫伊丽莎白
Elizabeth.
我已经很久没有念过她们的名字了
I haven't said their names out loud in a long time.
卡尔德 即使我想要帮助你
Kaulder, even if I wanted to help you,
我也不知道从哪里入手
I wouldn't know where to begin.
想一个可以关联起你我的词
Think of a word that you associate with me.
什么都可以
Could be anything.
把你的脑海放空
Empty everything else out of your head.
把思想集中在那个词上面
And just focus on that one word.
一个词
One word.
告诉我那个词 我也会把思想集中在它上面
If you tell me the word, I'll focus on it, too.
有时候这招会管用
Sometimes that helps.
那个词是什么?
What's the word?
孤独
Alone.
抓住我的手
Take my hand.
这边来 伙计们!
This way, men!
多兰兄弟 看
Brother Dolan, look.
卡尔德
Kaulder.
那是什么? 多兰?
What is that? Dolan?
小心点
Tread with care.
他做到了
He did it.
他成功杀死了黑巫后
So ends the Queen.
以父之名...
In the name of the Father...
他被附身了!
He's possessed!
卡尔德还活着
Kaulder is alive.
我们的噩梦在奇迹中结束
Our nightmare ends with a miracle.
帮帮他
Help him.
那是她的心脏
It's her heart.
一旦我们摧毁了它 她就灰飞烟灭了
When we destroy it, we destroy her.
你来摧毁它吧 多兰兄弟
End it, Brother Dolan.
消灭她 多兰!
Destroy her, Dolan!
不!
No!
你竟然保留了它
You kept it.
结束了 黑巫后死了
It's over. The Witch Queen is dead.
他们从一开始就背叛了你
They betrayed you from the start.
所以他们会折磨你的朋友
That's why they tortured your friend.
因为他知道心脏的所在之处
Because he knew where the heart was.
他们要复活黑巫后
They're gonna bring back the Queen.
八百年了
For eight hundred years,
我们一直在等待她的归来
we've waited for her return.
你应该感到荣幸 叛徒
You should be honored, traitor.
你将为我们的大业献出生命
You will be sacrificed for our cause.
卡尔德 我知道贝利亚把那些土带去哪了
Kaulder, I know where Belial brought all that dirt.
他租的那辆卡车有定位功...
The truck he rented had a standard GPS locator...
你骗了我!
You lied to me!
你保存着她的心脏 "回忆你的死亡"
You saved her heart. "Remember your death."
不是你想的那样
It's not what you think.
你一直知道这句话的意思 却什么也不说
You knew what it meant all along, and you said nothing.
因为我不希望自己甫一上任
Because I wasn't going to be responsible
就让十字斧教分崩离析...
for the dissolution of The Axe and Cross on my very first...
他们要复活黑巫后
They're bringing back the Queen.
你不知道自己干了什么
You don't know what you've done.
我曾宣誓过要保守秘密
I swore an oath to keep it secret.
数百年来 这秘密牵制着末日的降临
This lie has kept Apocalypse at bay for hundreds of years.
我们害怕一旦黑巫后的心脏被毁
We were afraid if the Queen's heart was destroyed,
你就会失去永生 甚至死亡
you'd lose your immortality. Or die.
那不是由你们说了算!
That wasn't your choice to make!
老多兰就是那么想的
That's what the old man thought.
我想他被攻击的那晚
The night he was attacked,
曾想要摧毁它
I think he was going to destroy it.
为了你
For you.
为了让你自由
To set you free.
至少十字斧教还有他们的武器
At least The Axe and Cross still has their weapon.
你将为黑巫后效命...
You will serve the Queen...
不 拜托了
No, please.
不管愿不愿意
like it or not.
去我的公寓 那里很安全
Go to my apartment. You'll be safe there.
不 说好了我们两一起行动的
No, the deal was that we stick together.
我要一个人去 连自己人都不可信
I'm going alone. If I can't trust
又凭什么相信你?
my own people, how the hell can I trust you?
你不是这样的人
This isn't who you are.
我就是这样的人
It's all I am.
用铁刺她
Pierce her with iron.
用火烧她
Scour her by fire.
让她永远的死去
Bring her endless death.
我很想念你 卡尔德
I've missed you, Kaulder.
这就是你不明白的事
Here's what you don't understand.
你的族人永远都不会明白的
What your kind never understood.
我已经饶过你一次
I've shown mercy.
我本可以把你们全部杀光的
I could have killed every last one of you.
我计算过
I've done the math.
我有过机会的
I've had the time.
你现在和以前不同了 如此自信
You're different now. So confident.
全靠你赐给我不死之身
Maybe you shouldn't have made me immortal.
卡尔德 我是来帮忙的
Kaulder, I came to help.
克洛伊 我告诉你不要...
Chloe. I told you not to...
不死之身从来都不属于你 它是我的
Immortality was never yours. It was mine.
你只是替我保管它
You just carried it for me.
直到现在
Until now.
我重生了
I am reborn.
你的种族
Your race
终日都在担惊受怕
has always been frightened.
藏在洞穴里
Hiding in caves.
挤在火堆旁
Huddling around fire.
终于
Finally.
嘿 孩子 我还在担心是不是太晚了
Hey, kid. I was afraid I was too late.
但愿我的样子没你那么糟
I hope I don't look as rough as you do.
好了
Okay.
我杀死了诅咒你的人
I killed the one who cursed you.
来
Here.
把这个喝了
Drink this.
谢谢
Thank you.
黑巫后复活了
The Witch Queen has returned.
我以为我的不死之身
I thought my immortality
是她惩罚我的方法
was the way that she punished me.
但她只是利用我来为她保存生机
But she just used me to save it for herself.
我恐怕也难逃其咎
I'm afraid I bear some responsibility.
我们太狂妄自大了
It was hubris to think
竟以为敌人发现不了我们的秘密
that our secret wouldn't be discovered by the enemy.
我预见到接下来会发生什么
I've seen what comes next.
死亡
Death.
黑巫后会散播新的瘟疫诅咒
The Witch Queen will cast another plague curse.
能散播瘟疫的巫师竟没有被摧毁吗?
Haven't covens with that kind of power been destroyed?
如今我们不摧毁巫师了
We don't destroy witches anymore.
我们囚禁他们
We incarcerate them.
我们把世界上
We took all the most powerful witches
最厉害的巫师们抓起来
that ever walked the Earth
并把他们放在一个地方
and put 'em in one place.
巫师监狱
The witch prison.
他们一直等待着被释放
And they've been waiting, waiting to be released.
等待着复仇
Waiting to exact revenge.
我们创造了完美的巫师团
We created the perfect coven.
现在我又回到了原点
Now I'm right back where I started.
你打败过她一次
You defeated her once.
你一定能再次打败她
You can defeat her again.
卡尔德
Kaulder,
你必须去
you must go.
你必须战斗
You have to fight.
卡尔德
Kaulder.
我从未给它起过名字
I never had a name for it.
但我的敌人管它叫"海克森贝因"
But my enemies came to call it "Hexenbane."
斩巫剑
Witch Slayer.
我也要去
I'm coming, too.
我们的协约是我保证你的安全
Our agreement depended on me keeping you safe.
不 我们的协约是如果我帮助你
No, our agreement was that if I helped you,
你保证我的安全
you'd keep me safe.
如果我现在受伤 它不会自愈的
If I get hurt now, I stay hurt.
你要怎么办?
Where would that leave you?
我才不在乎呢!
You know, I don't care!
谁说巫师不能追杀巫师了?
Who says that a witch can't hunt witches?
克洛伊
Chloe.
卡尔德
Kaulder.
这是什么?
What is this?
瘟疫之树 她就在这里
It's a plague tree. She's here.
咒语完成后
When the spell is done,
蝇群就会被释放
the fly swarm will be released.
我们时间不多了
We haven't much time.
跟紧了
Stay close.
卡尔德 囚犯们都去哪了?
Kaulder, where are the prisoners?
天啊!
My God!
我抓获的每一个巫师
Every witch I ever caught.
都被黑巫后当做了释放瘟疫的力量之源
The Queen's using their power to release the plague.
怎么做到的?
How?
咒颂
The chant.
没有巫师能强大到
No witch would be strong enough
独自承担这个咒语的作用
to cast this spell alone.
但黑巫后把他们的思想
But the Witch Queen's
像链条一样连接起来了
linking their minds like a chain.
我们该如何阻止他们?
So how do we stop them?
每个链条都有弱点
Every chain has a weak link.
- 我来杀死他 - 不要
- I'll do the honors. - No.
我们需要消灭的不是他的肉体
It's not his body we need to destroy.
是他的思想
It's his mind.
但如果他死在了梦中
But if he dies in his dreams,
瘟疫就能被阻止
the plague will be stopped.
我希望还有别的办法
I wish there was another way.
当我回来后你还会在这里 是吧?
You'll still be here when I get back, right?
你要和黑巫后单挑 是吗?
You're taking on the Queen alone, aren't you?
这必须有个了结
It has to end.
嘿
Hey.
在里面注意安全
Be careful in there.
你现在又开始关心我了啊?
So are you worried about me then?
我已经习惯你了
Well, I've gotten used to you.
追杀愉快
Good hunting.
你也是
You, too.
守卫
The Sentinel.
不把囚犯关进牢里
And it won't stop until this prisoner
它是不会停的
is put back in his cell.
它是冲着埃里克来的
It's coming for Ellic.
卡尔德?
Kaulder?
如果她出现了受伤的迹象
If there's any sign she's getting hurt in there,
你必须要把她唤醒
you have to wake her up.
向我保证你会把她带到别处
And promise me you'll get her as far away
越远越好
from here as you can.
没问题
Of course.
咒颂停止了
The chanting stopped.
她成功了
She did it.
一个梦行者能为你展示过去
A dream-walker shows your past.
但只有我能向你展示未来
Only I can show the future.
你会失败 人类将要灭绝
You will fail, and humanity will fall.
我已经统治世界了
I've taken this world back.
还没有
Not yet.
你能感觉到吗?
Can you feel it?
你的肉体凡胎?
Your mortality?
你的生命正在流逝?
Your life ebbing away?
爸爸!
Father!
卡尔德
Kaulder.
你们是我们世界的入侵者
You are trespassers on our world.
爸爸!
Father!
我从你眼中就能看出来
I've seen it in your eyes.
你渴望死亡
You wish for death.
你知道永生的好处是什么吗?
You know the benefit of eternal life?
就是我能杀死你两次
I get to kill you twice.
住手!
Stop!
卡尔德!
Kaulder!
现在...
Now...
- 克洛伊... - 很抱歉
- Chloe... - I'm sorry.
放走我的皇后
Release my Queen.
在我小时候 你从巫师手中救出了我...
Those witches you rescued me from when I was a kid...
他们没有杀死我父母 他们就是我父母
They didn't kill my parents. They were my parents.
不幸的是 我生来就没有魔法
But sadly, I was born without magic.
你是个巫师
You're a witch.
对
Yep.
- 不要! 不要! - 回来!
- No! No! - Get back here!
离他远点! 放开我!
Get away from him! Let go!
梦行者
Dream-walker.
看看你
Look at you,
真是个肮脏的早晨
you ugly bitch of a morning.
你最后背叛了
You turned against those
你被要求保护的人
you were charged with protecting.
是的 女王陛下
Yes, my Queen.
使我完整 祝我成功
Make me whole. Help me reach my destiny.
赐予我魔法吧
Grant me the gift of magic.
陶土不可能变成黄金
Clay cannot be turned to gold.
没有魔法 你就是一个凡人
Without magic, you're just a human.
父亲?
Father?
亲爱的
My love.
你必须站起来
You must get up.
父亲 你得站起来
Father, you need to get up.
拯救他们
Save them.
去吧 我的爱人 战斗吧
Go, my love. Fight.
你不肯放弃自己可悲的人生
You cling to your pathetic life.
为的是什么?
And for what reason?
最亲近你的人背叛了你
Those closest to you betray you,
你宣称要保护的人们根本不知道你的名字
and those you claim to protect don't even know your name.
以铁
By iron
和火焰之名
and fire!
你倒是用iPad拍死它试试
Try doing that with an iPad.
卡尔德!
Kaulder!
卡尔德?
Kaulder?
只要黑巫后的心脏还在跳动
As long as the Hexen heart beats,
她就永远不会真正死去
she's never truly dead.
不 你不能! 你会死的
No, you can't! You'll die.
我已经准备好接受现实了
I'm ready to face that reality.
不行! 一定还有别的方法
No! There must be another way.
听我说
Listen to me.
当我被拉进阴影时
When I was pulled into the shadows,
我看到了比她还糟糕的东西
I saw that there were things much worse than her.
她们在黑暗中 等待着
In the darkness. Waiting.
等什么?
Waiting for what?
一个没有你的世界
The world without you.
我们还需要你
We still need you.
我需要你
I need you.
十字斧教背叛了我
The Axe and Cross betrayed me.
我谁都不能相信
I can't trust anyone.
你可以相信我
You can trust me.
这条路我走了800年
800 years I've been on this road.
终日追杀
Always hunting.
- 终日... - 独身一人
- Always... - Alone.
你不会的
You wouldn't be.
另外
Besides,
你还欠我五万块钱呢
you still owe me fifty thousand dollars.
是五千块
Five thousand.
噢 想讨价还价哈?
Oh. So we're negotiating, then?
十字斧教会因为黑巫后的心脏
The Axe and Cross would be bothered that
不再受他们掌控
they're no longer in possession
而十分烦恼的
of the Queen's heart.
我以后不为十字斧教效命了
I don't serve The Axe and Cross anymore.
这次我是为自己活着
This time I do it for me.
嗯 是时候了
Well, it's about time.
你知道吗 我曾经觉得
You know, I used to think
宇宙万物只是无休止的轮回
the universe ran in endless circles,
永远都在重复自己 永远不出预料
always repeating itself, always predictable.
现在呢?
And now?
我不知道下一步会发生什么
I don't know what happens next.
你知道我们凡人管它叫什么吗?
Do you know what we mortals call that?
生活
Living.
知道吗
You know,
我还是需要你
I still need you.
那好
Well, then
愿意为您服务
I'm at your service.
来吧 你又不会变年轻
Come on. You're not getting any younger.
所以你准备好出发了还是怎么?
So you ready to go, or what?
我开车
I'm driving.
好
Okay.
支持我们，欢迎购买VIP移除所有广告，具体：www.OpenSubtitles.org